

+91-9050932477



adityagoyal619@gmail.com



https://aditya-goyal.netlify.app/



SUMMARY

Hey, I'm a software developer with 10 years of experience. For the last 5 years, I've led a team to build digital credential infrastructure in HR-Tech. I've also worked on ed-tech projects in JS full stack and as a .NET/SQL developer. As a hobby I like to work on latest JS stack and create meaningful interfaces for local businesses.

EDUCATION

National Institute of Technology

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2010 – 2014

TOP SKILLS



Exp - 5 years

I have worked as a fullstack developer on various edtech projects and also worked as a consultant to develop meaningful web applications in react.



Exp - 5 years

Created serverless functions in node which supported a realtimeDB powering modern web applications. Also used node to write migration scripts and to do performance testing using k6 library.



Exp - 5 years

I have developed a complete microservice architecture in springboot from scratch which facilitate a digital credentials repository to over 100k individuals

Other Skills - Docker, NextJs, Mongo, SQL, Shell Script, Productivity

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Engineer

eLockr, OnGrid | 2020 - 2024

- Created a scalable microservice architecture in Java Springboot, holding 10m+ digital employment, education and reference credentials for 100K+ people.
- Developed value added services like oauth, credential verification, ex-employment services using technologies like keycloak, kong, typeform resulting in revenue \$1m+.
- Developed and nurtured a team of engineers, grew team from 5 devs to 35 devs.

Founder - EdTech

LeapWired, EasyEd, Future Cadets | 2015 - 2019

- Created applications for remote learning, mentoring and gamified quiz platform using Angular, Ionic, React, React Native, NodeJs and Firebase.
- Collaborated and created a franchise of 35+ centres of remote learning across India.
- Created a complete web application for content delivery of course using react.

Software Developer

Fiserv | 2014 - 2015

- Optimised batch processing of app loading on the core product using concurrent pipelines in .NET to improve loading time by 80%.
- Worked on shifting of a large scale banking solution from SOAP architecture to REST APIs